Hello,
hello friends, welcome to Stroke. Friends,
some very good news has come from Sean Penn.
Yes, friends, just a few days
ago, the company announced its quarterly
results date. This is also
very
good news for their shareholders. So, without wasting any time, let's go to the
company's official note
and find out when its quarterly
results will be released and what the good
news is for its shareholders. So,
friends, we will go further to the company's official note. In
this notice, the company had filed a change.
You can first see that
a meeting has been set by the company's board of directors on May 10th.
For this, the company's non-serial research, i.e.,
Asian Paints' Water for
Cardinals, is going to be released on May 10th. This is
clear. And here is the good
news for its shareholders.
Friends, you will get a different income, that is,
extra income directly in the bank account.
But first, two points will be considered in the board meeting on May 10th, and
then the approval of its shareholders
is also necessary because this is the final decision.
After all this is passed, their shareholders will
get the deferral. By the way, I would like to say one thing that
once the deferral is settled, then
maximum 4 deferrals are to be given, the
board gives its approval and the share
holder also gets the approval. So
friends, this was a small bag but it is a
big one for the share holder of Asian Paints.
So I thought that it is
very important to convey this information to you people, so I
made a small video. If you
liked the information, then do like this video
and if you are new to this channel, then
keep this channel subscribed so that the
updates of your favorite company reach you quickly. So that's all for now,
we will meet in the next video, till then
goodbye.